KHUSHBOO GUPTA

Unity Programmer khushboofromindia@gmail.com

Phone No: -9871330054

India

LINKS

Portfolio

https://khushboogupta17.github.io/

https://github.com/khushboogupta17

Linkedin

https://linkedin.in/in/Khushboogupta17

SKILLS

Unity2d, Unity3D, C#, Github, Jenkins, Ruby, Bashscript, ARcore, ARFoundation, firebase, SQL, C++, Shadergraph, Photoshop, Illustrator, Blender

EDUCATION

Computer Science BTECH (June 2017-June 2021) CGPA-9.02

COURSES

- 1. Introduction to Game Developemnt by Michigan State University May 2020 - July 2020
- 2. C# Survival Guide on Unity Learn August 2020 -December 2020
- 3. Multiplayer FPS by Brackeys(backed by Unity)

April 2018-May 2018

4. Tower Defence by Brackeys(backed by Unity)

May 2018-July 2018

SUMMARY

Experienced game Programmer having tried hands in 2D, 3D and AR games. I have worked on advance C# concepts like scriptable objects, delegates and design patterns. I have knowledge of various data structures and have implemented dialogue systems, puzzle creation from environment and runtime mesh generation system.

EXPERIENCE

1. Software Engineer at Zynga

May 2021 to Present

Joined Zynga as an intern and after twice promotion at SE2 level now. Working on their highest grossing game CSR2, I have worked in boldbeat, prototyping and tools pod gaining experience of both backend and frontend architecture.

2. ViDoor (Personal Project)

December 2019-December 2020

An AR indoor navigation app implementing concept of graphs and shortest route from source to destination. It was a team project where I led the team and created the runtime graph creation functionality and storing it in firebase for future access.

3. Don't Lose... (Personal Project)

(October 2019 – December 2020)

AR message driven puzzle game where player gets locked outside its house and someone trapped inside, guides them to enter into the house through clues. Here You can watch the little clipping here

4. Snowy Laws(Internship at Stellenar Pvt Ltd.)

June 2019-August 2019

2D side scroller mobile game having both endless mode and challenge mode with simple controls like jump and slide. Implemented Object Pool design pattern to randomly generate obstacle at fix intervals. Uploaded on playstore.

5. Color Pencil (Internship at Intellisense Ltd.)

March 2019 – April 2019

It is Level mode and endless mode 2D mobile game Inspired by Color Snakes by ketchapp, build complete game in a month in the guidance of a mentor. Have a look here.

6. Spherothon (Internship at International Organization of software developers)

Dec 2018 – Jan 2019

Spherothon is a 3D mobile casual game available at google playstore. It has simple controls of right and left swipe to cross the levels. Uploaded on playstore.

<u>ACHIEVEMENTS</u>

- 1. 2nd runner up position at Unite India hackathon'19 from 400+ entries
- 2. Won 5+ Hackathons with more than 200 entries
- 3. Awarded Grace Hopper Celebration India student scholarship 2020
- **4.** Was part of panel discussion at IGDC 2022 on Journey to Game Dev.
- 5. Impacted 100+ students in unity Game Development
- **6.** Given 10+ workshops and interviews on game development
- 7. Designing student assistant at Teach India for 1 year